https://canadianlabour.ca/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Canadian Labour Congress
Media fr RSS
SubscribeTake ActionWhat We Care AboutWhat Unions DoWho We Are Media fr Subscribe
Search
Privacy PolicyPrivacy and DisclosureThe Canadian Labour Congress (CLC) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its web visitors. Any personally identifiable information we collect will be used solely by and for the Canadian Labour Congress and will not be shared with any other party unless you have given explicit consent to the disclosure or the disclosure is permitted under the Privacy Act. We will never sell or trade mailing lists for commercial purposes, nor allow any of our external suppliers to sell or trade our mailing lists.Submitting personal information to the Canadian Labour Congress means you are giving the CLC consent to use your personal information in accordance with the privacy notice statement. When you register for a conference or event, subscribe to a printed or web-based information delivery system, you consent to the CLC contacting you with information on other events or services we may offer and you may opt out of receiving communications from us by unsubscribing on the email you receive.Use of External SuppliersThe CLC uses external service providers for some projects that may include the collection of personal information. As a result, some personal information may be stored on computer systems owned and operated by these outside providers. These service providers are bound by contract with the CLC to treat all personal information they receive in a manner consistent with the CLC’s Privacy Policy and the provisions of Canada’s Privacy Act. The CLC will not, as a matter of policy, contract with external service providers who store data on computer systems operating outside of Canada, in order to ensure the provisions of Canada’s Privacy Act are respected.DisclaimerWe have attempted to ensure that the information contained in this site is accurate, relevant and up-to-date. We cannot, however, assume responsibility should errors or omissions occur.Links to other web sites: The CLC web site may contain links to other web sites. Those web sites are not under the control of the CLC and are provided solely for the convenience of users. The CLC is not responsible or liable for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by other sites. We encourage you to examine each site’s privacy policy and disclaimers so that you can make your own decisions regarding the accuracy, reliability and correctness of material and information found on linked web sites.Copyright and Trademark ProtectionThe contents of all materials on this site are the property of the Canadian Labour Congress. Distribution for commercial use without permission is strictly prohibited.The contents of this site may be viewed, downloaded, or printed for personal, non-profit and non-commercial use only. The CLC requests that if you use the content in a document or other publication (print or electronic) for personal, non-profit and non-commercial use, that attribution and recognition be given to the Canadian Labour Congress.
The Canadian Labour Congress reserves the right to disallow use of its content at any time.The name Canadian Labour Congress, the logo of the Canadian Labour Congress, as well as any/all of the related names and graphics are the property of the Canadian Labour Congress and may not be duplicated or used without permission. Commercial use is strictly prohibited.Stay up to date on issues that matter to Canada’s workers. Enter Email
SubscribeTake ActionPharmacare#DonewaitingEventsWhat We Care AboutBetter Pay and BenefitsEnding DiscriminationGender EqualityJobs, Economy and EnvironmentRetirement SecuritySocial JusticeTrade and International AffairsWorkplace Health and SafetyWhat Unions DoBuild Worker PowerPeople Working TogetherStrengthen Our CommunitiesContact a Union OrganizerWho We AreHistoryAffiliatesFederations of Labour and Labour CouncilsOfficersConventions and ConstitutionLabour Education
PublicationsCareersContactPrivacy PolicyMember Login Copyright © 2019 Canadian Labour Congress
